<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>English Posts on 张晶: Kristen Jing Zhang</title><link>https://kristenjz.com/en/posts/</link><description>Recent content in English Posts on 张晶: Kristen Jing Zhang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 19:51:04 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kristenjz.com/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Critical review: On digital divide and digital rehabilitation for formerly incarcerated people</title><link>https://kristenjz.com/en/2023/05/10/digital-divide-and-rehabilitation-released-citizens/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 19:51:04 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://kristenjz.com/en/2023/05/10/digital-divide-and-rehabilitation-released-citizens/</guid><description>This critical review was a course assignment in Dr. Reisdorf&amp;rsquo;s 2023 Spring COMM6000: Technology and Criminal Justice.
Introduction ​ This critical reflection examines previous studies about the ICTs use of returning citizens during their reentry into society and transition from former incarceration. The United States has incarcerated a great population of people since 1970s, with the imprisonment rate increasing throughout the 20th century and reaching 450-680 per 100,000 people by the start of the 21st century (Garland, 2001).</description></item><item><title>Book review: On the Run: Fugitive Life in an American City by Alice Goffman</title><link>https://kristenjz.com/en/2023/02/21/book-review-on-the-run/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 14:14:29 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://kristenjz.com/en/2023/02/21/book-review-on-the-run/</guid><description>This book review was a course assignment in Dr. Reisdorf&amp;rsquo;s 2023 Spring COMM6000: Technology and Criminal Justice.
Introduction This critical reflection reviews Alice Goffman’s (2014) book On the Run: Fugitive Life in an American City. It explores the impact of mass imprisonment in the US on young Black people in a Philadelphia ghetto. The imprisonment rate rose throughout the 20th century and reached 450-680 per 100,000 people by the start of the 21st century (Garland, 2001).</description></item><item><title>Lit: The references I will give if I organize a lecture on information seeking</title><link>https://kristenjz.com/en/2022/06/03/information-seeking-references/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 18:25:19 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://kristenjz.com/en/2022/06/03/information-seeking-references/</guid><description>Information seeking is when people find an interest or knowledge gap in one area and then acquire new information. It&amp;rsquo;s a concept in information science but has gradually become important in communication studies, especially in scientific communication, health communication, and other applied communication studies.
Here I&amp;rsquo;m gonna give a list of references on information seeking when I wrote my research on the same topic . These references help me a lot while building the concepts and models in the study.</description></item><item><title>CS: Markdown Testing</title><link>https://kristenjz.com/en/2021/01/07/second-post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 13:37:57 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://kristenjz.com/en/2021/01/07/second-post/</guid><description>See the source code of this page if you are interested.
H1 H2 H3 H4 H5 H6 List Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Table Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water1 Water Water Water Water Quotes What I cannot create, I do not understand2.</description></item></channel></rss>